{
	"Vocabs": [
		{
			"Question": "Basic consonants (14)",
			"Answer": "ㄱ ㄴ ㄷ ㄹ ㅁ ㅂ ㅅ ㅇ ㅈ ㅊ ㅋ ㅌ ㅍ ㅎ"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㄱ",
			"Answer": "g,k"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㄴ",
			"Answer": "n"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㄷ",
			"Answer": "d,t"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㄹ",
			"Answer": "r,l"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅁ",
			"Answer": "m"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅂ",
			"Answer": "b,p"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅅ",
			"Answer": "s,t"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅇ",
			"Answer": ",ng"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅈ",
			"Answer": "j,t"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅊ",
			"Answer": "ch,t"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅋ",
			"Answer": "k"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅌ",
			"Answer": "t"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅍ",
			"Answer": "p"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅎ",
			"Answer": "h,t"
		},
		{
			"Question": "Basic vowels (10)",
			"Answer": "ㅏ ㅑ ㅓ ㅕ ㅗ ㅛ ㅜ ㅠ ㅡ ㅣ"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅏ",
			"Answer": "a"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅑ",
			"Answer": "ya"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅓ",
			"Answer": "eo"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅕ",
			"Answer": "yeo"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅗ",
			"Answer": "o"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅛ",
			"Answer": "yo"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅜ",
			"Answer": "u"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅠ",
			"Answer": "yu"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅡ",
			"Answer": "eu"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅣ",
			"Answer": "i"
		},
		{
			"Question": "Double consonants (5)",
			"Answer": "ㄲ ㄸ ㅃ ㅆ ㅉ"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㄲ",
			"Answer": "kk,k"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㄸ",
			"Answer": "tt"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅃ",
			"Answer": "pp"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅆ",
			"Answer": "ss,t"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅉ",
			"Answer": "jj"
		},
		{
			"Question": "Double vowels (11)",
			"Answer": "ㄲ ㄸ ㅃ ㅆ ㅉ"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅐ",
			"Answer": "ae"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅒ",
			"Answer": "yae"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅔ",
			"Answer": "e"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅖ",
			"Answer": "ye"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅘ",
			"Answer": "wa"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅙ",
			"Answer": "wae"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅚ",
			"Answer": "oe"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅟ",
			"Answer": "wo"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅞ",
			"Answer": "we"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅝ",
			"Answer": "wi"
		},
		{
			"Question": "ㅢ",
			"Answer": "ui"
		}
	]
}
